{
    "id": "4a297d5384944e2cb0da86ec8a537f94",
    "title": "Verb conjugation exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ebe73e6c276b494daedb040070a42b8c",
            "title": "Verb Conjugation",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Maya ............................................ since morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is working",
                        "works",
                        "has been working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ...................................... in the garden, when he arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am working",
                        "was working",
                        "worked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................................... in the garage for three hours when John called.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "have been working",
                        "was working",
                        "had been working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ............................................. my exam this time next week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be writing",
                        "will write",
                        "would be writing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They had already left by the time I .............................................. home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "reached",
                        "have reached",
                        "had reached"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘I’m hungry.’ 'I .......................................................... you something to eat.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am getting",
                        "will get",
                        "will be getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Merlin .................................................... lovely songs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "writes",
                        "write",
                        "written"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ........................................................ often go to the cinema.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't",
                        "doesn't",
                        "haven't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ...................................................... to Philadelphia last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "went",
                        "have gone",
                        "had gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children ........................................................ a splendid performance.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "delivers",
                        "deliver",
                        "delivered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}